FEDERICO VILLAGRAN

UX/UI Designer

+34 662689581

(H)

www.federicovillagran.com

 \square

federico.villagran95@gmail.com

in

linkedin.com/in/federico-villagran



Madrid, España



WORK EXPERIENCE

ROBINSUN

Madrid 2023 -

www.robinsun.es

SANTANA CAFÉ

Montevideo 2019 - 2022 www.santanacafe.uy

PLATERO I EÑA

Montevideo 2018 - 2019 www.platero.com.uy

GENETICA TOTAL

Montevideo 2017 - 2018 www.geneticatotal.com

Business Developer / Marketing

Marketing: Website manager. Lead and manage website creation projects, tools and functionalities. Illustration of pages, manuals and documents. Marketing project management. Metrics analysis.

Business developer: Market analysis, prospecting and lead generation, negotiation and closing deals.

Co - Founder & Director

Leader and owner of specialty coffee shop. Responsible for collections and payments. Leadership and team training. Building links with potential brands. Communication in social networks. Company Accounting. Creation of new business ideas.

Today the company continues without my presence since I am looking for new challenges outside the country.

Sales Manager

In charge of looking for new points of sale, supervision of sales, deliveries and collections. Responsible for positive after-sales relationship with customers

Sales

Local manager. Public attention. Control of stock and imports.

Basic accounting control.

EDUCATION

IRON HACK

Madrid, Espana 2022

ECONOMY CCEE

Montevideo, Uruguay 2015 - 2020

UX/UI Bootcamp Academy

Tech academy focused on tech and design. I seek to portray my creativity as an entrepreneur in the technology sector and enhance the UX area.

Faculty

Focused on the area of accounting and business administration

ABOUT ME

Passionate about learning and facing new challenges. I always seek to train and improve myself in the professional area as well as as a person. I consider the interpersonal bond within a company and when doing business to be

very important.
Businessman and entrepreneur with experience in business management, accounting, corporate finance and team leadership.

SKILLS

- Team leadership
- Empathy
- People skills
- Proactivity
- Design thinking
- Strategic thinking

PROGRAMS

- Figma
- Google Analytics
- Myro
- · HTML/CSS
- Hotjar
- Notion
- Excell

LANGUAGES

- Spanish Native
- · English Professional
- Portuguese Professional